webcuk.co.uk 2016-06-01

# Privacy Policy & Data Protection - WebCreationUK

**Our promise**  
WebCreationUK will respect your privacy and ensure that all sensitive and personal information provided to us is lawfully processed and held in accordance to the Data Protection Act 1998. Personal/sensitive information is deemed to be any information that identifies a living individual. 

****Controlling your information****  
WebCreationUK will control the data you supply and we agree to collect and control this information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. WebCreationUK contact information can be found on the contact page of our website. 

****How do we collect information?****   
We collect information from you when you submit an enquiry, visit our site, call us for information and send us an email. The information we collect is: 

  * Your name
  * Your email address 
  * Your company name, address, telephone and fax number 

Using your information 

We will only use the information you provide us with to: 

  * Make improvements to our service 
  * Action any requests you make 
  * Supply you with requested information 
  * Conduct market research 

WebCreationUK will not sell or share your personal data with others. 

**Accuracy**  
WebCreationUK endeavor to keep all personal information that they store up to date. We will amend any information we find to be inaccurate or are informed is inaccurate at our earliest convenience. 

To ensure com pliance with the data protection act 1998 WebCreationUK are happy to supply you with any details they hold about you. There is a £10 admin fee for requests of this nature. 

**Online activities**  
WebCreationUK collect information from your visit to our site. This information is only used to track browsing patterns and cannot be used to identify you personally. 

**Security**  
To prevent the unauthorized access or disclosure of your personal information WebCreationUK have put in place all reasonable Physical, electronic and managerial systems required. If you are asked to enter sensitive personal information pertaining to payment details WebCreationUK ensure 128bit SSL encryption is in place via our merchant provider. 

**Changes**  
WebCreationUK reserved the right change this privacy policy at any time.
